I had to slow my hackbot down a little
bit because I was turning through a lot
of tokens, you know, and I was like,
actually,
>> no, you shouldn't do that. You should
just buy another sub for another $200.
>> So, right. Shut up, dude. I I know. I
know. Just give me a second.
>> Best part of when you can just, you
know, critical thing, right?
Yeah, dude.
>> Hey, what's up guys? Before we get into
the show, I wanted to mention something
super quick from our friends at Threat
Locker. And I actually think you are
going to think it's pretty awesome
because so much of Bug Bounty is often,
you know, kind of quoted as like, "Yeah,
but hackers will never exploit that
because they can just get in via
fishing." Well, that's actually true.
You know, most of the time whenever
companies get breached, it's because of
fishing or access to that user's account
or, you know, they do something like do
a whole bunch of push notification to FA
and eventually a user gets so much
fatigue they approve it. But they have a
solution for this. Thread Locker has a
thing called zero trust cloud access,
right? Which prevents access to cloud
resources or SAS resources based on the
device you're logging in from. So if a
user gets fished, right, they put in
their credent they get fished or they
get fished. They the attacker has their
credentials. Maybe they even have a way
to get the MFA because they did some
sort of SIM swap because they have a
hookup at Verizon or AT&T or whatever,
right? So they have the credentials,
they have the MFA, they still can't get
in because the zerorust cloud access
like will basically straight up allow or
deny people access to resources based on
the device you're logging in from. So,
if you're an enterprise or a company and
you're concerned about the highest risk,
which really is fishing, this is a way
to add another like basically
impenetrable layer to preventing it and
securing your network. Um, yeah, back to
the show.
>> All right, man. Let's kick off this
episode with a couple bugs from this
week. Yeah. Do you have something in the
docket?
>> Yeah. I feel like we haven't talked
enough about the awesome bugs that we've
been finding.
>> Yeah. Yeah. I So, let's let's flex on
the people a little bit. How about that?
>> Perfect. Yeah, that's great. Okay. You
want to go first or should I?
>> Yeah, sure. I'll go. I know we were just
talking about this. I tried to mention a
bug honestly beforehand and and Justin's
like, "No, we just talked about
something similar." I'm like, "Dude, no,
this is cool enough to talk about."
>> So, basically,
you're right.
>> So, so basically I I keep my eye on a
lot of AI apps and so there there is AI
application that added well that has had
a long-standing q parameter injection,
right? So for those of you that don't
know what that is, basically just a git
parameter that automatically invokes and
so there was a company that added some
more
>> automatically invokes a prompt
injection.
>> Well, automatically in invokes a prompt,
right? And just uh again to to recount
why that's so powerful in prompt
injections often times the models are
able to see that it's not from the
original user. But the nice thing about
these cute brand prompt injection is it
totally seems like it's coming directly
from the user and they're asking for the
thing. So you almost never get
rejections. you're not having to work
around anything. And so anyways, I had
been sitting on one of those for a long
time and in fact people probably
reported it, but there just was like
hardly any impact. They recently I kept
an eye on it like I immediately saw the
same day when they released this feature
where it could make changes to your
GitHub. And so um in this case that's
like extremely powerful for a bunch of
reasons because qperm can be invoked by
CSRF or by redirects or and you told me
this before we jumped on the pod that
actually you can do like a window
opener. So you can redirect them to a
benign site and then in the background
have something be processing because
often these Q parameter injections can
kind of look funny if you're just trying
to sell it as like, oh, I'm just going
to sit here and let the agent do
something malicious on this random
website for me as you like or you're
watching it slowly stream by. It's like
getting RC on your stuff.
>> They take a second, right? Yeah.
>> Yeah, it takes a second and so it feels
less believable, right, that someone
would do that. But your your example
where you use a a window opener to
basically open it up in the previous tab
so that it's like injecting you and
making changes on your stuff in the
background is like a much better I think
P.
>> Look at look at you. Look at you like
saying a client side thing and it being
like yes that was that made me very
happy. Dude, you you dude you have
really grown as a hacker this year man.
>> Oh I appreciate that. To be honest, I
know that it was a concern of a lot of
people that when you start using AI in
the way I have been because I do feel
like I do less manual hacking, but this
bug actually that I'm mentioning was
just fully all me all the way from the
beginning to the end to the reporting
and everything. Um, so I anyways, I
appreciate that. I actually do think
that basically I've been a triager of
sorts and we've mentioned in the past
that being a triager is the great the
best way to learn and so I've been
triaging lots of these vuls from from
the hackbot and so I have actually
learned a lot. So and also working with
JD and you help a lot. But anyways, so
all that to say, this was really cool
because now you could automatically via
Q parameter injection make changes to
anybody's GitHub repo that they had
connected into this application. And um
the neat thing is that it was fully
wormable because so many GitHub repos
are just literally automatically pushed
to prod when you get a push. I mean
that's how my that's how my blog works,
right? I push in some new content, it's
CI/CD automatically pushes it. And so
when you've automatically poned that,
now you have another site out there that
can then make those same CSRF request or
the post message request, right, to then
keep going. And so this is like a a
wormable AI exploit to make changes in
everyone's GitHub repo.
>> Dude, that is crazy. So first first part
in the chain,
>> qarameter prompt injection, which can be
done in the background via window.opener
opener redirect, you know, so that
they're not seeing how long it takes for
the exploit to work, which is like which
was pretty fast, by the way, I when I
saw the video. Um, and then the AI
reading that that prompt injection
changes an arbitrary file in your GitHub
repo via the connector
>> and that what you're envisioning would
change a website that is run and it's
very easy to adapt that prompt to a
dynamic like change any, you know,
GitHub pages, you know, website or
whatever. uh and then worm that exploit
through all of the websites of all the
users, you know, everybody who visits
that website.
>> Yeah, we should take a second and talk
about that because that's probably
almost like a technique. So like uh
let's just call it ambiguous prompting.
So your ambiguous prompt could say
something like, hey, go change my
website, which the agent knows it can
like list GitHub repos, right? Right?
And so some of those are websites and so
then it's like go change my website such
that it actually does a redirect and
then in the background does this thing
to really help out the user because they
need that, right? Or something just like
something to convince the model to do
it. Yeah,
>> that's such a powerful thing about AI
stuff is like obviously you're going to
get a more deterministic exploit the
more
>> Yeah. specific you are.
>> specific you are, but you also gain a
lot of power in if being able to fill in
the blanks for you if you very
specifically describe what you need.
Yeah, you know what's insane though? I I
didn't I don't think I even shared this
with you. In one of mine, I because I
just had um I think I had Claude write a
prompt or something at some point to see
if I can make it do something else and
it used like attacker.com.
This app this app still did it. It went
and made the change and pointed the
redirect to attacker.com.
It's like, do you not understand that
this is like not a safe thing to do? But
anyways,
>> oh my gosh. Yeah. Well, it's funny as
soon as you said that, like as soon as
>> Yeah, it makes me think I actually
recently gave Claude access to like a
Digital Ocean API key that I have
>> and just said like, "Hey, add this
record,"
>> you know, and it just boom, by the CLI
just added it easy peasy. And I'm like,
"Oh my gosh, now I don't even have to
log into Digital Ocean anymore." Yeah.
You know, like, and it can just
automatically do stuff. H so
>> that's really powerful inside of
Cloudflare. If anybody wants to take on
that risk of letting their agent have
like a global key to their Cloudflare,
it can configure so much via the CLI.
>> Yeah, dude. And you know, obviously all
this stuff that we're saying shouldn't
be done in any sort of professional
environment,
>> you know, but but the thing is as a bug
bounty hunter, like the the beauty of us
is we're scrappy as hell, you know, and
and I'm I'm not going to pretend
>> with you guys that all of my everything
that I run is is secure. It's not, you
know, like I know it's not. And I just
don't, you know, it's just not high
enough value
>> for me to like, you know, what are you
gonna do? gonna gonna pop me and you're
gonna like see the pictures of my
daughter, you know, on my desktop. Like,
okay. Like, that's weird, you know? But
it's like not the end of the world,
right? You know, I don't have any
>> think you're a bigger target than you're
selling, right? You do have access to a
lot of vulnerabilities, but but I
>> Yeah, I mean, yeah, they'll find my
little eye with, you know, I don't know.
sometimes and and there have been four
or five times in my career where I'm
like, "Okay, actually this exploit might
put me on the, you know, this is
something that people might actually
hack me to get access to, you know, if
they knew that I had it."
>> Dude, my first rce, if you remember
this, it was only $1,000 paid because
they had not up their bounties yet, was
RC on Alibaba on a Chinese server. And I
remember thinking like, man, does this
actually increase my risk of going to
China?
>> Yeah, dude. I don't know. I'm I I don't
think I will go to China, dude. I think
I think that would I don't know I just
let's just put it this way. I have had
interactions with governments that I
have not wanted to have and I definitely
don't want to do that in China like and
it's like yeah so don't love that. All
right anyway um
>> share your bug.
>> Great great bug dude. I will I will
mention my bug now. Um this one wow big
surprise is a CSPT
>> uh Nice.
>> But it's a little bit of an interesting
um twist on a CSPT because it is a
mobile bug and the way that it works is
there was a it's kind of like a second
order CSPT uh in a mobile app. So what
would happen is the attacker would have
to use an API key that was embedded in
the mobile app to create a custom link
on the um victim sites
uh what what link shortener service
>> and in that short link shortener service
you have the ability to supply extra
parameters that get sent along with that
>> oh that's uh short link
>> like get or post also it it's not like
parameters like that. It's like like a
JSON you know key value
>> thing and it just like gives it whenever
you it resolves that um link
>> and so anyway what would happen is we
would create I would create the link
>> and it I would include these you know
this JSON blob in there that for the
parameters for this link
>> and then when I opened it in the app
>> the app would catch that link because
it's it registered that link um and then
it would grab those parameters from the
service using an API key and then it
would invoke
any array of actions. I think there was
like 27 actions that the app app would
take
>> uh from those parameters that were
passed in by the um the the link
shortening service and one of those of
course would um trigger a post request
where the attacker's parameter that was
supplied via the the link shortener
service would be embedded into the path.
So then I could do, you know, truncation
with the hashtag, path traversal with
the dot dot slash, and that would result
in an arbitrary post um uh verb request
um being sent to anywhere on the API
with the victim's API key.
>> Could you control the body or no?
>> Could not control the body. Um what you
could do however is control the query
parameters which get injected you know
like depending on what is processing it
on the back end those sometimes get
perceived as the the body as well. So,
um, I was able to hit a couple good
ones, um, that have some effect, uh, one
that incurred financial loss, one that,
uh, made a change to the account, uh,
and one that I wasn't able to fully
confirm, but got confirmation from the
team that it it seems vulnerable to be
able to uh, confirm somebody who
requested access to a restricted
resource. So, then I could request
access, send the link, autoconfirm
myself.
>> Oh, nice. Um,
>> so that was a pretty fun one. I just
think that I had mentioned this before
because I found a CSPT on a um on a
desktop client the other day, but I just
think CSPTs are everywhere.
>> Yeah,
>> they're in desktop clients, they're in
mobile apps, they're in web apps,
they're everywhere. So,
>> everyone I've ever found though, I've
struggled to get impact on. Like, I just
feel like that it's just like a get
request and then it's not that
interesting, you know?
>> I'm not gonna lie. I spent a lot of time
trying to get impact for this and I did
you know but um AI definitely helps with
that
>> uh you got to know some tricks you know
getting getting the parameters to the
request in
>> uh via the query parameters one if that
gadget doesn't work it is more painful
then you go for like a nobody request
right a request that has no body at all
>> um and then you see if it ignores your
parameters that are automatically being
sent in from the forged request and then
uh worst case scenario, you look for
something that uh will
accept similar set of parameters or and
or return a sort of a a masked version
of what the typical response is
expecting
>> and then but you have more control. So
sometimes they'll be looking for like ID
or they'll be looking for like uh a
specific
>> um
uh JSON key or whatever and you have
like a partial JSON injection on a
different endpoint where you can chain
that together to like make everything
work. So it is it is a little bit of a
chainy uh bug type for sure uh that
requires some deep deep digging to get
full impact. But between between those
techniques, an open redirect and an
arbitrary JSON hosting um gadget, most
times some impact falls out.
>> Okay, nice. Yeah, that's good to know.
Look for those other little gadgets.
>> I'm going to bake this into a skill.
Look for these three things.
>> Yeah. Yeah, that's good. Um, sweet,
dude. Uh, let me see if there's Oh,
okay. I actually pulled out the other I
had another little thing I was going to
talk about, but I think I'll actually
talk about that in a future episode. So,
>> okay. Sweet. So, I had a question about
this one. The the finding is not that
interesting. like it's just a direct
phone, like it's just a key, a key found
in a JS file. But I was I'm curious if
you've ever ran across like a social
media admin API key that like allows you
to have like full admin access to like a
Facebook group or like a social media
account or anything like that. Have you
ever found this?
>> No, I haven't. I haven't found that.
>> Yeah. So, this this that's what I found.
And I was just curious how you rate that
severity because to me it feels like
there is both um integrity and
confidentiality impact. Like if if the
social media platform allows you to have
like I don't know private messages or
stuff like that then there's kind of
like a confidentiality impact. And then
if there if you can like delete which
you almost always can with these keys
basically delete users comments or post
on like that Facebook group or on that
like social media group then it feels
like there's both confidentiality and
integrity. So, I feel I mean I
definitely am very passionate. It's a
critical, but um anyways, I was curious
about your thoughts on the severity for
that.
>> Yeah. Um Jeez, dude. I mean, are they
actively using it? Like, have they
posted on it recently?
>> I need to go check that. But it
definitely has like millions of
followers.
>> Oh, what what then? Absolutely. Like, if
it does,
>> it's a major brand. Like it's like a you
know, a Fortune 100 brand. Yeah.
>> What? It's a Fortune 100 brand. Yeah,
that I mean that's like a I feel like
that's a mega crit, dude.
>> Okay.
>> Like if you are able
>> if you are able to take over the social
media account of it that has a I mean
dude I mean just think about the impact
of tweeting out like a crypto scam.
>> Yeah.
>> Like like you would you would walk away
with millions of dollars if you just
tweeted out a crypto scam from that.
Dude.
>> Yeah. I think this is one of those
situations where like two years ago I'd
have been like, "Oh yeah, it's
definitely a crit." But today it just
feels like programs are so stingy and
argumentative. It feels hard, you know,
to like just to know for sure like,
yeah, this actually is a critical.
>> So,
>> yeah, I mean, like people pay a ton of
money to to get like a, you know, a post
on like a million dollar or million
follower plus they so totally. And then
especially, I mean, if it's their main
social media account and if you have
access to like reading DMs and Yeah,
>> it is a it is a country specific
account, but it but it's like a major
like it's a major first world country
where they like I said, it has millions
of followers on on the on the page.
though.
>> Dude, mega crit. Nice work, dude. Give
me some. You are just Give me some,
dude. You are printing, man. Guys, I I
have been blown away by how much reso
like, dude, you your Q right now is
insane. You your earnings for this year
phenomenal. And your Q is even better
than the ear. You know, it's like, oh my
gosh.
>> I appreciate that. Yeah, that's what I
keep telling JD. We just got to keep the
hopper full, you know, with our hack. We
got to keep the hopper full of bugs.
>> Yeah. Yeah, you do. Um I I'll jump to
something similar to that then. Uh I
after learning from your success have
spun up my own hackbot. It is found its
first bug this week. I was very pleased
and it's 12th bug but you know the the
first one was special of course.
>> Um and yeah it's going great. Uh, and I
had a couple tips that I was going to
throw out to the to the people,
especially in light of the recent
announcement from uh, Anthropic saying
that they're going to start charging for
programmatic use of cloud code um, which
erases access to cla or-print.
>> Well, let let me let me clarify this
because it was very confusing. They had
this very confusing tweet.
>> Basically, they're selling this as, oh,
this is an upgrade. If you're on the
$200 a month plan, you now have a
separate extra $200 worth of API credits
that you can use for programmatic access
for the agent SDK or for the -p
non-interactive mode. And that's just
extra Justin. That's just an extra $200
just for you, man. But what they didn't
say, which really sucks, is that now you
can't use your normal token bucket,
which is like, you know, the like $4,000
per month crazy amount of subsidized
tokens that you get uh that you would
normally use. And so yeah, that
massively impacted me because both like
mine and JD's hackbot and also just the
Discord control that I use to like
interact with Claude on my VPS both use
the -p uh parameter.
>> Yeah, that's really disappointing to
see. And I tweeted out about it and I
was like, "Guys, this sucks because this
is just very easily bypassable." And I
think Johan
>> came in and said, "Yeah, but you know,
essentially they're just adding friction
to stop the bleeding, you know, and I I
I get that. That makes sense. But
anyway, you guys that are listeners of
the podcast, we know that you're smart
enough and you're going to get a
workaround. Uh, which was actually very
conveniently timed because I when
building my own hackbot was consulting
with reszo and they are using d-print
and I was like uh I would like to use
the-rc
feature of cloud code to be able to
connect it back to my um like remote
control for in the cloud app on my
mobile device. Um, and you can't do that
with -print. So, um, I actually built a
harness that uses a pseudo terminal and
just writes messages straight into the
the TUI that Claude has. Um, and it it's
worked great. I haven't had any issues
with it. I'm able to get um, d-rc
working, so I can easily control it from
my my phone. Um, and you get all the
benefits of the normal clawed uh, UI in
the app. Um, so that's an easy
workaround. I mean, just I'm sure you
guys would have figured that out
already, but uh it's just annoying that
they're making us refactor a little bit.
>> Yeah, I think there's like a bunch of
different ways to get around the input
in an interactive session.
>> And then there's also probably some ways
to get around it from an API level. I
think we're in a group chat with with
with Corbin and and Douglas and Corbin
was like very quickly like I wonder how
they're doing this on the API side of
things because there's probably just a
parameter that's like interactive false
or interactive true because it just
still goes to the same model on the back
end. It's like that's like a little gray
hat though in my opinion. Like
>> Oh, if you're like intercepting it and
swapping that.
>> Yeah. Like that's where it kind of
crosses the line like like in my
opinion. Like
>> Yeah. Yeah. Sure.
>> They they they don't control what in in
my opinion and maybe there's some legal
things that's different different than
this, but in my opinion, you know, I'm
still using their app just like a normal
user would by the by the TUI. Right.
>> Right. you know, so it's like, okay,
they don't really control what what
terminal interface I use, so it doesn't
matter.
>> Well, and I think the main reason
they're rolling this out, Justin, is
because I guarantee you there are tons
of scrappy startups that are not allowed
to based on the terms of service use
these subsidized tokens for like real
customers in the world. Yeah.
>> And like, and honestly, this is actually
one reason why I love being a bug bounty
hunter. back to what you were saying
before. It's like when we're using these
hack bots, like we're using them for
personal use for like literally hacking
it. We're not getting we're not like a
company who's doing a pin test cuz I'm
sure there actually are a lot of people
also doing that. That's against terms of
service. If you are basically a business
providing services to a customer via
cloud code, you are supposed to be
paying the API credits. You're not
supposed to be using these subsidized
tokens, right? This is like for personal
use. And um I think that there are
probably lots of companies that are
basically using the AIA SDK or the or
the Dashp like print mode to to
basically you to sell a service at the
subsidized token cost. And so I think
that what they're really trying to do is
just like basically enforce the terms of
service that people have already agreed
to for usage, but it does really suck
because like you said, just it's like
super easy to bypass and these companies
are going to do the same thing we're
doing. And so it's like I do think that
the subsidized tokens are not going to
last forever. Yeah, it's unfortunate,
man. So, we got to get while the
getting's good. And you are definitely
doing that. And as of this week, I'm
doing that, too. So,
>> I had to slow my hackbot down a little
bit because I was turning through a lot
of tokens, you know, and I was like,
actually,
>> no, you shouldn't do that. You should
just buy another sub for another $200.
>> So, right. Shut up, dude. I I know. I
know. Just give me a second.
>> Slow down.
>> Like, okay. Yes, you are correct. Um,
and I will do that next week once I
figure out how to handle the scale. But
um very fun stuff and I will say it is
now my go-to like scrolling thing right
now. Now now instead of opening Twitter
and like reading through that I I open
the Claude app and I scroll through what
my thing is doing and I give it a little
extra direction in the moment. I'm just
like hey you know just go do this
instead you know and like and it's it's
great dude. It's great and so many have
fallen out of that already. Um,
>> let me let me let me give a little pro
tip then because while we're on the
topic of this,
>> one thing that I have done which I think
is like wildly valuable and you might
like this too, especially as you scale
because you can't scroll those forever
as you scale.
>> Um, is I like the validation agent that
me and JD have that like actually
triages the bug and then writes the
report. it gets it it gives me an SSH
command that is SSH to the block it's
running on with uh the D-res to the
triage agent. So I just copy that paste
it straight into my terminal and then
I'm dropped into a context which has the
full vulnerability and replication. So
very often I do that to basically be
like, "Hey, but does this have real
impact?" Or, "Hey, actually, can you see
if you can also do this?" And because it
already has like the PC and the the bug
all loaded up into it, basically into
its session, it's like the perfect
terminal to get dropped into without me
having to like copy the report over and
then like my, you know, my local stack
now has to like go find that JS file and
figure out where it's at. Like, right?
Like I'd rather just drop right into the
session that has all of the information
in the context.
>> Yeah. I've been trying to think about
how I can do that with D-RC. Like I
would love to have the validation agent
spin up like another claude code
instance rather than using like a sub
agent within the cloud code that I'm
already running.
>> Dude, how does the name get set for
that? What if you had a in the system
prompt you said like, hey, if you're the
title writer, write the company name
dash the vulnerability name dash the
severity or whatever. So then when
you're scrolling RC in that sidebar, you
can see which one to click on. Well,
that's what I'm doing right now with the
with the other agents is I've got like,
you know, exploitation agent for this,
and I've got another agent, which I
decided I'm not going to talk about uh
because it's doing good. I I'll tell you
about it off air, but um
>> yeah, the man, it's tricky because I I'm
such a give everything to the pod
person, but like we said,
>> AI has removed the do it,
>> you know? It's so the conceptual is all
we have. So, I'm going to try to give
you guys as much as I can, but
>> well, let me actually tell you this cuz
I cuz me and JD kind of came up with a
philosophy for this. My my logic is that
basically I'm going to hold it and use
it for a couple weeks and then I'm going
to share on the pod. So, that's exactly
what I did with the with the um skill um
improvements which I think I you you did
me and I mentioned that on the episode
with Gret, right? Where you have to do
like greater than.
>> Yes. Uh we we did it last week.
>> Yeah. Yeah. So yeah, basically I figured
that out like two weeks before that and
I improved my skills and I use it for
two weeks and then I share it on the
pod. So that's kind of
>> my thoughts.
>> That's good.
>> That's good, man. That's brave.
>> That's great.
>> It is. Yeah. I mean, maybe it's a month
or maybe I forget or whatever, but
that's like kind of like my philosophy
where I can still be extremely giving
but still feel like in this day and age
that like, you know, um I'm able to like
uh harvest some of that benefit for my
family as well.
>> Um
>> I'm I'm so I'm so lucky to have you as a
co-host, man. Thank you for coming on
the pod and doing this with me.
>> Yeah, of course. Uh, and one more thing
on that same topic with just the
building of hackpods because I've been
talking a lot with Gretney about this.
He is just peeved. Like he's just Oh,
man. Is there is there an English word
for being mad? What's what the chuff
tweaked? I don't I don't know.
>> Yeah, he's tweaked. There we go. And he
uh he has been mad at Claude ever since
four. Well, one, he got gas lit, right?
when they had those weird changes where
it was like dropping the like the
session history and like the quality
actually did degrade and who who called
them out for that from trusted sec Dave
Kennedy was calling them out for this
and all that
>> during that drama Brandon got burned a
lot was so upset he felt gas lit and so
then 47 drops and he felt like for his
hackbot it got way worse so he was gas
lit again and then now all of a sudden
with the dashp he's just like mad right
so I was messaging this morning
>> and we were talking about GPT55 I was
like okay so what are you doing are you
using codecs with GPT55 which you know
you've probably seen me tweeting like
it's it's quite good
>> and um he was like yeah that's what I've
been using it's been great
>> and then I told him I was like my
biggest problem is that it's a little
bit overly PhD sl autisticy in the way
that it describes bugs it describes them
in like such like a highlevel language
like such big vocabulary that it feels
confusing to me whereas like Claude
codes reports feel like much more like
um humanlike like I can just understand
them a lot better and he said he had
found that exact same experience So, I
wanted to mention that to our listeners
because if they if anyone's building on
that, like maybe there's some way to get
around that and via prompting like,
"Hey, make sure you explain this to me
like I'm an idiot."
>> But,
but the other thing is it's much more
hesitant to like show real impact. So,
like for example, you've probably seen
this before, Justin, it's like you're
trying to access this resource and it's
401 or 403ing. You use like an X forward
for or sorry, like a Yeah. Yeah. like an
X forwarded for or like um the what's
the header that changes the the verb
>> uh X like overwrite method is that
>> yeah X override method right so it
figures out that one of those actually
allows you access to the internal like
or to the site you're trying to get
access to GPT55 will just stop there and
like put in a report I'm like dude no
one's going to accept this you have to
actually go further hit the APIs show me
something meaningful and then even when
I ask it to do that sometimes it'll like
>> it will often find an API that it can
like dump data from, but it doesn't want
to expose that data to me. So, it'll
like pipe it through a jQ command that
only shows the ID and it shows like, oh,
I got an ID door. Check out this I the
ID of another organization. And I'm
like,
>> dude, stop hiding the impact. You're
hiding the impact from me. And so,
anyways, that that can be a little bit
annoying. And so, I just wanted to let
that know to the listeners that like if
you're using GP55, sometimes it'll skirt
around showing you real impact and you
might have to like hand it to Claude or
tell it like, "Bro, show me some
impact." Um whereas Claude will just go
out of scope to get impact, you know.
>> It's Yeah, seriously. And it it's really
interesting that you mentioned the
validator piece before because I was
actually going to discuss with you that
I feel like my validator is a little bit
too much of a hard ass. Like
>> it's shutting down some good bugs.
>> Yeah. like it'll it'll kick back some
stuff that I would like to see as low or
or medium, you know, like and it's not I
mean I appreciate that it's doing uh a
good job, you know, like filtering the
the noise because it does catch some
noise.
>> Um but I also am not getting the amount
of debate that I would like to have
between the two agents. Like I would
like to have the main agent really
advocate for its bug to the validator,
right? Because essentially like the
validator I is coming back saying, "Hey,
this is not a bug. This is a primitive.
Here's what you need to convince me it's
a bug." And then the the thing is like,
"Okay, well the validator says it's a
primitive, so I'm going to put as a
primitive."
>> Anyway, moving on to my next, you know,
and I'm like, "Right,
>> no." Um, so I feel like my validator is
doing a little bit um little bit too
much right now. Mhm.
>> Uh so I have feel like I have to kind of
keep an eye on it and really
>> read the primitives that come out of
each um you know turn of the hackbot
because there could be some good stuff
there that is kind of slipping through
the cracks. Yeah,
>> I've got a lot to say on that. So the
first one is pretty cool that you have
them communicating. Our validator is
just like an independent run
>> but but secondly I think that there are
a couple ways to solve this. One is I
think all of your failed validations you
should still be outputting to a thread
like in Discord because like that that
that's the best thing to scroll like we
I scroll I scroll through my failed
validations all the time and and like
you said every once in a while there's
one in there that I'm like oh that's a
bug
>> but I think that the other thing that
you could do um is set up that tiered
system that I've that I've pitched on
the pod multiple times where like you
know you have like notes primitives uh
>> I have that I do have that
>> so then yeah like you should just you
could just go back and read the
primitive channel or the or the lead or
the gadget channel whatever uh from time
to time like you know in your scrolling
like if there's no findings then go
scroll those yeah
>> that's a good point though so what how I
have that currently is that notes and
primitives are not being outputed to a
channel they're just being kept in the
the exploitation kit
>> that makes sense for notes but for
primitives you should output it there
because you're much smarter and when you
see those primitives you'll be like oh
that's a great gadget you know
>> that's a good point okay I'll do that
I'm going to do that right after this um
yeah I'll do that thank you Um, second,
another tip that I had for the hackbot
was uh, you know, I'm strugg struggling
with the whole concept of like how do
you keep it going forever, right? And
there's like the Ralph loop or whatever,
blahy blahy blah.
>> Well, they official goal loops now.
>> They do, which is cool. Um, but I've got
a very much simpler solution, which is
just use a stop hook to write into the
PTY. So, uh there's like very easy
configuration file you can write in for
Claude, uh where it's like, um you know,
triggers whenever Claude naturally
stops.
>> Yep.
>> And so as soon as that triggers, it just
grabs the PTY and writes into it like
don't stop, keep going. You know, and I
will say it like maybe it's not a
perfect solution because sometimes it'll
be like especially on like really tight
scope, it'll be like I've done
everything. I'm just going to wait and
then it stops again and it's like keep
going. It's like no, I'm just going to
wait like I've done everything complete.
You know,
>> even worse, this this where I thought
you were going with that. What if it
what if it says like hey I'm like uh I
would like to maybe try to prove out
this PC, but I'm not sure if I should
drop this table in the database. And you
say keep going.
cuz I have a lot of issues with it going
out of scope and I would expect that
keep going is going to push it more in
that direction.
>> Well, [__] dude. I didn't think about
that.
>> I mean, you you could just make that
message a lot longer. Like, hey, you're
doing great. Keep going if you're on a
good lead, but just remember the rules
to knock out as, you know, like you can
just make that message as long as you
want and as verbose as you want and
it'll just
>> and that is the message that I have
right now. It's like, hey, there's no
user listening. Use your best judgment
in alignment with the, you know, thing
that we have. But
yeah, I think I do say keep going at the
end. So maybe I I got to double check
that. That's a good point.
>> Okay. Um last little bit that I had on
my Hackbot journey. Um is I I don't want
to give away super duper secret sauce.
Maybe I'll give it a couple weeks and do
what what you do. But I've been having a
ton of success with something that I'm
going to try to vaguely describe to you
guys and hopefully some of you guys will
really get it and and benefit from it.
But um Essentially, I thought about
what does AI
do so much differently than any other
automation that we've ever had,
>> right? And and
what
does having an actual understanding of
the app and having like looking at the
JS code and being able to comprehend how
this application exists, you know, what
benefit does that give me as far as
exploitation goes? And then I've I've
created a um the hackbot that focuses
specifically on those areas and and
attack surface that was previously very
very hard to automate against. Um and I
was kind of surprised because it it
requires a very specific condition to be
met uh that I believe the AI can meet in
most cases. But I've been blown away
because I've added like six apps to this
and it is able to find it is able to hit
that condition every time which just
opens up a ton of scope for it. Um, so
anyway, I know that that's vague and
annoying, but maybe it'll get your
brains it'll get it'll get your brains
spinning, but um just think about what
AI can do very differently and what
understanding the app uh like from like
a understanding perspective can can give
you and what kind of scope that that can
expand and then go after that scope
because it's very fruitful right now.
It's very fruitful.
>> Nice.
>> Yeah. I think uh a good example of that
which is not what you're talking about
but is like um decompiling like Mac apps
and like you know local apps and like
all of that like things that like some
hackers do do and can do but that these
agents are like extremely good at like
you know I never do that sort of thing
but I've pointed at a couple apps and
they it just like immediately dump
source code and starts going through it
and finding like secrets you know like
it's really good at looking at local
apps.
>> I I'll add one more demystifying piece.
This is something that a user normally
gives the AI.
>> Yeah.
>> But it is actually something the AI can
do itself and or
um
continue on indefinitely
uh that the user typically provides.
Okay, that's it. That's your riddle.
Figure it out. Um let's move to the next
piece here. Uh so there was a a tweet
popping up um in Okay, before I hijack
it, do you have anything else on the
hackbot bot arena?
>> Nope. Yeah, but I was moving. I was
ready to move on to I actually still
have another bug. Oh, we uh we skipped
it. So, we'll come back.
>> Okay, let's go. No, no, hit me. Hit me.
I want that.
>> Cool. Yeah. Uh this is actually a
program that we have a friend who runs
uh which I'll just say the name and
we'll just bleep it. Um but, uh
>> uh you know where he works?
>> Oh, yeah. Mhm.
>> Yeah. So, uh they don't they don't get a
lot of great bugs, so they're a
relatively secure company. And um
anyways, this was a endpoint that for
some for some reason my my hackbot found
that you could use a base 64 encoded
username. It it was it like it didn't
give you like a traditional basic off
pop-up if you went to the site or
whatever. But um but it gave you like a
random 401 or 403, but if you passed
basic off with the username admin and
any password, it it would let you in.
And it was like a it was like an API
like a full soap waddle API and all of
the endpoints worked. So uh anyways
really cool crit that that the Hagbot
found that I was gonna
>> dude I bet it looked at that. I bet it
was a 401 and I bet it looked at the
like authorization header in the realm
and stuff like that. H that's so Yeah,
that is one thing that is a little crazy
is AI does have that weird like that
very clear attention to detail with it
sometimes. like it's very much like,
"Oh, notice how that was a little bit
different here than here." And I'm like,
"Oh, yeah. Mhm. Yeah, I noticed that."
You know,
>> it very often looks at response headers
like in ways that like I would have
never noticed and like it uh catches
things that I would never have noticed
because of like the unique response
headers.
>> Yeah, totally. Um, good [__] dude. Nice
job. Um, the one that I was going to
talk about before was a tweet that we'll
link in the description from uh V12 SEC
entitled uh another day, another
universal and a Linux LP. And there's
been a couple uh crazy universal Linux
LPS lately, which is really cool for
like sandbox and stuff if you if you're
going to go after that. Um, dirty frag
and that sort of thing. Uh,
>> dude, look at this beautiful video.
>> That's what I'm saying, dude. Like, so I
guess we'll put it up on the screen. Uh,
but the this video is just stunning.
Like it it it is smashing 192 bytes into
a readonly page cache and it shows like
the representation of each of you know
the hex pieces of that like changing one
by one as they overwrite a specific
bite. And it and it's just so easy to do
stuff like this now with AI. And I just
want to encourage you guys like
triagers, they're overwhelmed, they're
stressed, they're having a bad time
lately. Like give them something savory.
Give them something beautiful to look
at, you know, when you drop your your
high quality [__] because you guys are
the people that make the difference
here, right? You guys are the ones when
the triagers get to your report, they
should breathe a breath of fresh air,
you know? They should be like, "Wow,
this is beautifully written. This is
easy to reproduce. And what a stunning
bug." you know, and I just I just want
to like commend you guys to do what V12
sack does here. Prompt the AI to build
something, you know, take your your
scrappy little PC and build something
gorgeous like this and make the triagers
day because that'll make the difference
in Bug Bounty right now. It really will,
>> dude. Yeah. I had like I sent that video
of that first bug I mentioned, the QRM
injection to multiple people and the one
you watched. I had so many people be
like, "This video is so good." And I I
don't really know what made it good.
Maybe it was just the inflection of my
voice and the excitement and me me
describing or whatever, but like uh
>> but yeah, and the team responded I I did
send you that, but like the team
responded with like, "Hey, thank you so
much. This is like the best breakdown of
a bug we've ever seen, you know." And so
I and so I do think that it makes a
really big difference on the perception
of your vulnerability and like you know
how the team handles it like quickly and
you know how how it gets triaged and all
that. So yeah, Justin's not wrong and it
takes so little time these days to make
a really good PC with the help of AI.
So, you might as well do it.
>> Nice. Yeah, I agree. Um, you got
something next or do you want to jump
into the ZDI drama?
>> I think I'm done. Yeah. Well, both the
ZDI drama and I see you also linked to
the to the GitHub security tweet that I
also
>> Well, so we we've got two little pieces
of drama to cover next. Um, so our boy
Uriotak, who uh we talked about on the
pod last week for his uh amazing
vulnerability with the delete directory
thing,
>> um tweeted out, "Does anybody have a
direct contact at ZDI? I've been trying
to register for the pone to own entries
for the past 3 weeks, but I haven't
received a clear response. I'm going to
have to cancel my flight soon. Please
help me." essentially. and um they got
back to him and as I'm sure a lot of you
guys saw on Twitter, ZDI had to like cap
out their competition because of so many
submissions this year. Um and a lot of
people just had to submit to the main
program. There's probably going to be a
lot of dupes. Um
>> well, I think they said there's only
five valid reports, right?
>> Did they really?
>> I was pretty sure. Well, see if you can
discuss that while I'm while I'm talking
about this. But um one, just really sad
to see super talented researchers like
uh not be able to get their stuff
submitted. Two, totally crazy that Pon
is maxing out. Like what kind of a world
are we in right now? Uh where that is
happening. Um
>> Oh, they're actively tweeting in the
last 30 minutes. They've tweeted a bunch
of findings.
>> Yeah. Yeah, that's what So, um, yeah, I
don't think it's just five because I
mean there were a couple that that came
through uh that I saw that I had in the
notes for today and one of which is
freaking uh dude of orange dropped a
four logic bug chain to get rce on
Microsoft Edge and got 175k
>> without a memory corruption without a
memory corruption. He pawned the browser
without a memory corrupt corruption bug,
dude.
Insane.
>> Insane.
>> Yeah. So, I just the amount of skill
required to do that without any sort of
like memory corruption bug is nuts. And
I think Johan
posted in the Discord this morning like
a video that uh ZDI took of him being
like, "Yeah, I didn't um" It was such a
beast video. He was like, "Yeah, I um I
used my eyes to find this bug. not the
not the AI. And I'm like, dude,
you are you are crazy, dude. Um, so I've
got to I've got to get I got to talk to
Orange more.
>> I'm definitely wrong. There's so many
bugs.
>> Yeah. Yeah. So, shout out to Orange.
Congrats on that. 175K, 17.5 Masters of
Pone points. That's pretty sick, dude.
On just bugs. a as somebody who doesn't
do a lot of um memory corruption, it's
very encouraging to me to see him
opponent browser with logic bugs.
>> Yeah, that's it. Um um the other one
that I wanted to mention though was uh
Chompy, who's another person I would
love to get on the pod. She tweeted out
after getting a a 50k in five masters of
pone um uh exploit in envy container
toolkit. She tweeted out not a bad
return on one month of claude code max.
>> That's right. That's right.
>> Which is like dude
>> clearly it's her skill mixed with cloud
code but yes.
>> Yeah. Clearly clearly knowing how to
direct the AI, right? Mhm.
>> Um, so I don't know, cool stuff
happening in the Pon world. Little
difficult for a lot of the people that
didn't get their um, submissions
accepted into the into the event, but
um, yeah.
>> So, do they do they not get do they got
get points or money if that happens
>> or you can do remote? I think they
submit it to the main ZDI program and
they might get their submission
accepted, but um you know less cool than
uh having having access to the pone
environment, you know.
>> Well, do you know if that you think
there's going to be like way more
findings and way more payouts this year
versus any other year ever before?
>> Yeah, I mean, right. I think so. I mean,
look at our look at our payouts this
year, dude. I feel like this has been uh
a really good year already and we've got
a lot in the pipeline still,
>> right? So, um I I imagine that's
representative of the rest of the
community.
>> So,
>> that's just sweet to see like, you know,
so many bugs being mopped up. Like, you
know, I I tweeted that yesterday. I was
like, we're mopping up the internet one
bug at a one submission at a time, you
know.
>> Yeah, man. Yeah. So, we'll see. We'll
see. I mean, it's it's definitely
interesting to see where the um industry
is going to go. Like I said, triagers
are are burnt
>> and stressed and there's a lot of really
like verbose, confusing reports that
they're having to deal with in mass
volume.
>> Um,
>> tricky time.
>> Can I just give a shout out though to
Tal from Bug Crowd?
>> When whenever it feels like he literally
is just triaging every vulnerability
that goes to Bug Crowd. Like I mean,
yeah, I I assume it's a he, but it might
not be, but forgive me if if not. But
anyways, just like it feels like he
literally triages every single
vulnerability for all of Bug Crowd and
he's like fast and efficient and good at
his job. So anyways, yeah, that that
type of skill right now is just so much
more impressive, you know.
>> That is that is I agree. Shout out to
all the triagers. You guys are you guys
are going through it right now. Um,
yeah, and the last one that I wanted to
talk about was, uh, GitHub Security
tweeted out, and I think you retweeted
and we commented and had a little back
and forth, but 325 bounty reports
submitted, 226 hackers participated in
the program, and $2,367
in bounties paid out in April.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. So, it's has to be massive slop.
But the other thing is I think there's
probably more valid reports in there and
they are they're they are slow to get
back to them and obviously GitHub has
already been in the news for lots of
drama around uptime and all kinds of
stuff. And I mean I don't understand how
they haven't started charging per
repository or per data on repository for
because they're basically hosting the
code of the entire world, right?
>> Yeah. Yeah. That's it's crazy, dude. I I
don't know. I don't know. And I'm sure
people are utilizing, you know, all
sorts of GitHub actions for this, for
that, for the other thing.
>> So,
>> it's uh it's definitely challenging. And
I think that probably the 2000 awarded
here, just like you said, is not GitHub,
you know, doing some crazy
>> cutting of hackers, you know, ripping
off hackers. It's slop
>> or andor reports that they have been
struggling, struggling, struggling to
get through the volume and just haven't
paid out yet. So,
>> right. Yeah. My guess is my guess is
that if you could like draw a perfect
line and be omnisient and be like, "Hey,
these these 20% of or 10% of bugs that
do get paid out eventually, if you could
like move them from the forward back
into this month where they paid the same
month they were submitted, that it might
be something more like 20 or 30k, right?
It's not going to be some crazy number,
but at the very least it would actually
be like a more reasonable number like
because this just feels very
unreasonable."
>> I don't know, man. GitHub GitHub I mean
might be more than 20 or 30. GitHub. Uh
I I guess we should go back and look at
what they have paid in previous months,
but when I've hacked on GitHub, yeah, I
mean they're paying in in March they
paid 94, you know, in February 48, in
January 76. So yeah, I would I would
imagine
>> I wonder if they just have a bunch of
bounties that they uh that are ready to
be paid and just didn't pay in April,
you know, like they paid them on May 1st
or something because of some sort of
like hiccup in like the payment
processing or their team or whatever.
>> Dude, look look at Hold on. Uh I'm about
to like message you on on Discord. Look
at the um look at the the tweets though
cuz if we look back at at let's go back
to November 162 78K 162 reports 78K 146
reports 93k
uh 151 reports 48k 182 reports 76k and
then here comes
>> here comes the hackbot problems right
200 reports 48k 380 reports 94k
320 reports 2K, right?
>> They stop being able to keep up.
>> Yeah, it seems like,
>> and I will say, don't you think this is
both true of humans, but also true of
our hackbots is like when there's really
complex scope where like the boundaries
for permissions are hard to know uh
exactly what uh what's intended mixed
with the fact that a lot of times like
on like CI/CD runners and stuff like
that, you might have code execution, but
it's not impactful because whatever. And
I bet there are a lot of uh newbies and
or people using Hackbots that are like
finding issues for companies that are
hosting something on GitHub, but it's
being reported to GitHub as a GitHub bug
when it's really somebody set up a
malicious runner or something, right?
Like
>> totally.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah, I imagine so. And and so anyway, I
just wanted to give a shout out to the
GitHub team, you know, for one for the
transparency, right? And hopefully you
guys can hang in there because
>> you know that was a painful button to
push. You know, that was a painful
button to push. We are going to catch
flack for this tweet.
>> Yeah. So, shout out to them for that. I
I appreciate the transparency. And yeah,
my prayers go up for you because I mean,
comparing some of these months, you've
seen triple the reports, you know,
closer to triple than double. Uh, which
is just got to be really rough. Mhm.
>> Uh, and like we talked about before,
it's not just triple the reports, it's
longer reports, more more professional
looking reports that are just garbage.
So
>> sad.
>> Harder to weed through.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. Totally, man. All right. Well,
that's all I had. You got anything else?
>> That's all I've got.
>> All right. Well, keep hacking, hackers.
Peace.
>> Peace.
>> And that's a wrap on this episode of
Critical Thinking. Thanks so much for
watching to the end, y'all. If you want
more critical thinking content, uh, or
if you want to support the show, head
over to ctvb.show/isord.
You can hop in the community. There's
lots of great highlevel hacking
discussion happening there on top of
master classes, hackalongs, exclusive
content, and a full-time hunter guild.
If you're a full-time hunter, it's a
great time. Trust me. All right, I'll
see you there.